[{"answer": "Well, coming from you, Piers, that means a great deal to me, and I thank you for being so gracious.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "Why have you decided to face the music?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well, I think -- I think you've hit the nail on the head right near there, Piers.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "And I think a lot of people feel, wow, how could this have happened to them?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "I don't know if any of it makes sense, to be quite honest, Piers.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "And what -- I suppose what I'm getting at, does it really make sense to you?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "This is making me even sadder.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "How can you not love somebody?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "And but I was never made to feel so because they had four kids of their own, and those were the most important years of my childhood, because they -- it was that harmony that I would constantly refer back to, because my life after that, my mother -- my biological mother came to take me when I was four years old, and it was this strange woman who I'd never seen before.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "Yes, I remember that moment very, very well, because I remember she -- I remember -- I remember screaming all the way home on the bus to Brixton, which is where she was living with her new boyfriend.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "Do you remember that?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "Yes, my biological father, he came to take me and I live with him and his new wife, my stepmother, who I love dearly, and that was pretty much when the hell started.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "Biological father?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "By your father?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "Well, my father used to -- my father used to -- he used to -- there was one point where my father cut up six what must be -- must have been meter-length pieces of twine, something that you hang the curtain up with, and because I'd been suspended from school.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "When you say thrashed, how?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "Well, when you have kids, you realize that it's not the easiest gig in the world, but, yes, you're absolutely right, for all intents and purposes, I was a child.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Why should you be, after all this?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "No, the reason is, is that I don't want my kids to ever see that.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Is that one of the reasons why when you get smeared with this volcanic temper thing, it really annoys you, because actually the last thing you would be is like that, because of the way you were brought up?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "Are they aware of what's happening?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "Of course we have.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "You've told them?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Well, exactly, that's what I had to say.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "How good was he?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Well, you mentioned black president.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "What is the reality check about Barack Obama?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "As you were preparing this album, did you have any concept that that was how this was all going to play out?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "That, in of itself, probably gives you some insight into who I am as a person.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "You get the irony of this?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Were you aware when you -- as I say, when you put this together, was it anything to do with what was happening with your life at that moment?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "No, because we -- we -- I wasn't the only person who picked those songs.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Total coincidence?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Well, I had done an interview -- a TV interview in 2009 about John's charity Reaching Up.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Tell me why you decided, after all this time, to write it?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "You know, as I saw it develop, they sort of started out -- they had this little camaraderie.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "How would you describe the relationship, as you saw it develop?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Initially, I think it was very difficult because it was -- once they got married, it somehow amped up.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "But did she find it tough, do you think, being in the public gaze?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "I mean, I see Caroline from time to time at events or restaurants or -- it's always really nice to see her.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "Have you stayed in touch with the family at all?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Do you know how they reacted to the book, the family?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "He certainly talked about running for office at some point.", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "What do you think he would have been doing?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "Well, I think, you know, the legacy he left that was unfortunately, \"George.\"", "docId": "120127pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "And what will your lasting memory be of him?", "qSentId": 489}]